Well, did they sing in the Philippines,
did they sing the Christmas songs as well?
Yeah.
Can I say something?
What?
Look at me right now.
Santa doesn't go there.
No chance.
Yeah, he does.
Oh, really?
Imagine what Santa has to do.
Santa has to go to all the states, all the cities in America.
Yeah.
All of Europe.
You think he goes to America first?
No, definitely.
Yeah.
L.A. first.
Yeah, L.A., New York.
L.A., New York, Chicago, Atlanta.
He's done.
He's in London.
It's five, three in the morning.
Sun's coming, right?
Elf calls him.
You forgot to go to the Philippines.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
What is he going to do?
Bail.
Bail?
Yeah, he's going to bail.
He's like, I'm not going to get across the Pacific
and go to that little island.
What the fuck?
And what does it give you guys?
Pineapples and coconuts.
You guys pick those.
Pick them.
Sing it right now.
I want to hear it.